Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
NO ANIMALS WERE HARMED DURING THE
FILMING OF THIS PRODUCTION
Osman, where is my son?
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
My Savcı!
Thanks to God.
Where is my son?
Who is that?
Möngke!
My son!
How dare you take my son here as if he
is a prisoner?
We took him here the way he deserved.
Just like a rabid dog!
You’ve been looking for the one who
betrayed you.
Here he is.
You can call this dog, either your son
or a traitor.
It’s up to, Geyhatu.
Today is the day we become
victorious, sons of Romans!
The dice is rolled.
Today, for our holy lands…
… for our children’s future…
… and for our honor, we must fight!
If we lose this war, kill me at once!
Since it means…
… because of my pride, I sent you to a war
that we couldn’t win in the first place!
But today, I won’t be responsible for the
death of our Empire and my soldiers…
… but the Turks!
Today…
… the dice has been rolled.
The victory is ours!
Cerkutay told me that you kidnapped
my son.
Cerkutay, huh?
Yes, Cerkutay!
And you believed that, Geyhatu?
Are you trying to tell he lied to me?
You and your soldiers will enter the
secret path here.
And I will open the gate for you.
While Kayıs are busy with Geyhatu...
... we will take our Kulacahisar back!
Stop!
Just like you ordered, Alp Guards will be
poisoned and won’t be able to fight.
Look, something is happening to soldiers!
Helen!
Dear Helen, today is the day.
Today is our day!
Thanks to you, feudal landlord Nikola.
For the revenge of Sofia!
You know what to do, right Helen?
Don’t worry about that.
If I had come across to them…
… I’d have killed your son and your
soldiers.
Your soldiers were dead when I
arrived at the Tent.
And this traitor son of yours
wasn’t there.
Do you know where he was?
He was torturing me to find out how
I found the cave he was hiding.
What are they talking about, Möngke?
They are lying, father!
We still have lots of things to tell you.
Our minds are sharper than our
swords, Geyhatu.
Don’t you forget about this.
I will listen to you.
You only have one last chance to survive.
Geyhatu…
… you will either listen to fables which
will bring your death…
… or, to the facts which will make you
survive.
The choice is yours.
You must be Bamsı Bey.
Yes I am.
Now, open your eyes and be fair…
… so that my face won’t be the last face
you’ll see before you die.
I will listen to all of them in the Tent.
They will tell me what happened since
the beginning.
Alps!
My Rab…
… oh my Rab, grant our Bey to us.
Grant our Bey to us, my Rab!
Oh, the one who can give remedy and heal.
What happened to our soldiers?
Be ready and close the gates at once!
For Byzantine!
He is finally here!
In the name of our mother, Mary, and
our Lord, Jesus.
For Byzantine!
My son set a trap for me, huh...
... in order to kill me.
He was trying to pull you in Sögüt.
They were going to kill you in Sögüt and
blame my brother, Osman.
They are trying to use the hatred you have
for Osman who killed commanders of yours.
Can’t you understand?
Who exactly, Dündar Bey?
It seems like this deficient son of yours
didn’t plan everything by himself.
Enough!
Shut up!
Yalvak Arslan…
… do you have something to tell?
Ertuğrul Bey is like a father figure to
me and we are also from Kayı tribe.
I can't blame Ertuğrul Bey...
... just like I can't blame his sons.
The victory is ours!
Byzantine is reanimating once again!
How can you still listen to them, father?
Shut up!
Hush!
I listened to both sides.
On the one side of the scale…
… there are the words of your son...
… and on the other side, Kayıs’ words.
If you were me…
… what would you do, Bamsı Bey?
I wouldn’t believe the both sides.
Words are tend to hide away the
intentions.
Just like night hides away many horrible
things.
He who drowses the facts…
… and moves with words, eventually hits
the wall of facts.
Neither Savcı Bey nor Osman Bey and your
son…
… are not innocent unless they bring
evidence.
They say Kayıs are judicious…
… and I believe they are right.
Then, listen to me carefully, Geyhatu.
On the one side of the Scale of Justice,
there is your life…
… on the other side, your son’s life.
Now, with this case, you have to prove
that Genghis Khan is your ancestor.
Do you have proof for your words?
I gave you my life, father!
I fought, I got wounded, and I almost
died.
What else do you want?
Shut up!
Cerkutay...
..., while your son was torturing my
brother,...
... blurt out their plan.
Tell us!
When I asked your son how he was going
to kill you…
… he said Cerkutay is trying to pull
him in Sögüt and we sat a trap there.
Lie!
All they say are lies!
What are we going to do with the
prisoners?
They are going to pay the double amount
of gold they demanded for our soldiers...
... if they want them back!
I like making people pay, Flatyus.
May God protect you, Nikola.
Brave sons of Byzantine!
Cowards die for a thousand time
before death comes for them…
… but you were born for a thousand
time in this castle today!
Your manhood is equal to thousands
of cowards’…
… and you have more freedom than them.
Today, in this castle, you became
heroes for a thousand time!
The victory is ours!
All of them are lies!
Bring me Cerkutay.
My Alp caught him and they are coming.
He told us everything like warbler.
He will be here soon.
You will hear your own ears.
Your son said, “When the time
comes, I will kill Argun Khan.”
After that, I understood they were
collaborating.
He was going to blame Osman then wash his
blooded hands in our clear water.
And in the end, replace you.
You ruined everything!
I’m going to kill both of you!
Father.
Father, please forgive me!
Have mercy on me!
I made a mistake, Father.
Please forgive me!
I’m begging you, please forgive
me, father!
I made a mistake, father, please
forgive me!
I'm begging you!
Have mercy on me, father!
I knew Osman Bey wouldn’t come
back without Savcı Bey!
How could Osman Bey come back without
his dear brother, my Ahmet?
They’ll work together and
get us out of this mess!
You were angry at me because of Osman Bey.
You were going to rip my
tongue apart, Hazal Hatun.
Hatuns! We need to come
together. Enough of this!
Thank God our Beys
returned safe and sound.
Now it’s time to overcome
this trouble. Don’t.
Sorry, my daughter. Of course, if Osman
Bey came without Savcı Bey--
Möngke is traitor!
He wanted to kill Geyhatu!
Geyhatu killed him!
By punishing him, he reclaimed his honour!
Get him out of here!
Osman Bey and Savcı Bey saved our Tent!
2 valiant brothers on the same path!
Their story will be
graven on the mountains!
So, you didn’t catch Cerkutay.
You used his sinister name as bait.
I saw that Cerkutay was tricking you.
It was obvious that he
had his name in this.
You’re a smart man, Osman.
After you find Cerkutay,
you will see who is with him.
When that time comes, allow
me to have my revenge, Geyhatu.
You’ll be the first to find out.
You’re now free.
Say hello to Ertuğrul Bey.
His mighty sons will stay on
these lands like noble mountains.
That what I see.
Yavlak Arslan…
If there’s any disobedience,
you’ll be the one who pays for it.
Burn all of these.
Nothing of Turk’s will be left.
Dirty nomads.
Look at this. What are you even
doing with castles and city life?
Shepherd!
What were you doing in Kulacahisar?
I’ll set you free.
Under one condition.
Give me that!
Here!
You’ll tell everything you
see here to Osman.
Whatever you see word
by word! Look at my eyes!
Can you see how entertained I am? Can you?
Good. Will you tell him?
You will tell him! Right?
You. will. Tell. him.
Good. Long story short,
you will tell Osman.
Vulgar people.
Look at this. Shepherds.
Victory is ours.
I’d die for you, brother.
I never doubted your
intentions and I never will.
You made it on time. You’ve shaken
the enemy with your tricks.
We’re the sons of Ertuğrul Gazi,
brother. Doubt doesn’t suit us.
My brother.
Brother?
You’re okay.
Mashallah, my valiants!
As long as you stand
side by side, who can stand in your way?
Who can destroy your traditions
as long as you protect each other?
Mashallah, my valiants!
Brother!
Our father’s condition is bad.
Dündar!
Father!
Get our father up.
Osman, come.
Easy!
Father! Come on now, easy.
Brother!
Savcı.
Father!
- Savcı.
- Father!
Savcı.
Father!
Osman.
Where is Osman?
Father? I’m here.
I’m here, father. I’m with you.
I’m with you, father.
Father…
Don’t make me fall from your grace.
Don’t make me fall from your heart.
I’ll always be with you.
I’m always with you.
- Father!
- Father?
Savcı, let us deal with our father!
Father!
Osman! Come, brother!
Father, brother!
- Come on brother!
- Father!
Drink it, father.
Abdurrahman Gazi, make way.
I’m here to see how Ertuğrul Bey is doing.
His sons and brides are with him.
No one else is needed.
Yavlak Arslan isn’t anyone else.
Yavlak Arslan is the Bey of Beys!
My Osman! Do you see what
Abdurrahman Gazi is doing?
He doesn’t allow me to see Ertuğrul Bey!
What are you doing near Ertuğrul Gazi?
Osman! Osman, you’re forgetting
who you are talking to!
What am I forgetting?
We’ll see, Yavlak Arslan.
I didn’t forget what you did with Kuzgun.
I’ll not let this go.
If you’re behind this,
I’ll cut your head off!
What’s the matter, Arslan Bey?
Savcı Bey! Teach some
manners to your brother.
Teach him how to speak to Yavlak Arslan.
How can you tell someone who
challenged Geyhatu…
… not to challange Yavlak Arslan?
Kulucahisar has fallen, my Bey.
Nikola sent me to tell you. He wanted
me to tell you what he did to Turks.
What are you saying?
Son! Stop, relax!
Bamsı Bey! Let me go!
Let me go! I’ll rip his lungs apart!
- You don’t know what you’re doing!
- Let me go!
Relax, son!
The messengers who will take my news
to the Emperor are already on their way.
Everyone in Constantinople
will hear what I’ve done today.
They’ll say, “Nikola came yesterday
and took the castle today!”.
“I wonder what he’ll do if we
sent him new armies?”, they’ll say.
After destroying Kayıs, where will he take
the banner of Byzantine.” they’ll say.
Yes!
That’s what they’ll say. My soldiers
will be on patrol everywhere.
They’ll take care of every Turk they see.
Until there are no Turks left in Anatolia…
Do you think he'd send us
additional units, Vlatius?
We’ll enter Söğüt with this unit.
Kill every Turk in there.
Until there are no tents, no
goats, no shepherds left.
What do you think, Vlatius? Am I right?
Vlatius, isn’t that right?
An eye for an eye, Lord Nikola.
An eye for an eye, my dear friend.
An eye for an eye.
Let’s grind our swords!
Let’s go to Kulacahisar
after morning prayers!
Let’s conquer the castle we took with
our martyrs blood, for our martyrs’ souls!
You’re right, my Osman!
He’ll instead hear that
the castle is reconquered!
We wouldn’t be embarrassed.
Attacking a castle is different
from attacking Tents, Bamsı Bey.
Savcı, my son!
That’s what you think?
Attacking a castle is different from
attacking Tents, you say.
But, son, I know that castle well
since we took it with my Osman.
But it’s different this time.
There are prisoners in the castle. We
need to think about their lives.
Savcı Bey is right. We need
to get our minds together.
First thing in the morning, we should
get the Beys together to decide.
It’s important. We need to consult them.
I’ll be at the castle’s doors first
thing in the morning.
- Osman.
- Brother!
I am the Head Alp, Osman.
Osman!
They took the castle while we
were dealing with Geyhatu! Dogs!
They knew!
What will we do now, brother?
Alps!
Am I mistaken or are you
talking about what to do?
We’ll take our hostages back!
Bring the golds we took
from that Greek infidel.
My Bey. Will we give those
infidels gold like rewards?
I’d give everything in
the world for a Turk’s life.
Thank you, my Bey.
Instead of standing here,
sharpen your swords!
My Bey. What about Savcı Bey?
We’ll take the castle
back tomorrow, I said.
Thank you, my Bey.
We can’t rest now.
We’ll take what is ours back.
We will, with Allah’s permission!
- We’ll fly our banner!
- With Allah’s permission!
- We’ll conquer many more castles!
- Allahu Akbar!
We’ll found our Beylic in these
lands my father conquered!
- Allahu Akbar!
Brothers! Those who
believe are victorious!
Those who sharpen their swords with faith, stand
side by side, walk together are victorious!
Muslim Turks walking Muhammed Mustapha's
path, his highness, are victorious.
- Allahu Akbar!
Now!
Time to be victorious!
- Allahu Akbar!
Savcı Bey. What if Osman does something
without our knowledge?
Be at ease, Arslan Bey.
That won't happen.
It won't happen you say. Like it
didn't happen before, Savcı Bey!
I will happen again. This boy
will do as he knows again.
Arslan Bey! The one you call a boy
is Osman, son of Ertuğrul Gazi!
Choose your words carefully.
Everyone is mad. No one is in
the mood to listen to these words.
You are their elder.
You should be calm.
You're right, Dündar Bey. But in this
Tent, there's no respect...
... for elders or any titles.
Nothing has order.
Savcı Bey, you're the First Alp. How long
will you listen to Osman Bey?
This matter is different, Arslan Bey.
If he doesn't listen to me,
I'll break his bones!
He will not act on his own,
if he does, he will pay for it!
Seasons have passed since
the little one was born.
Yet he couldn't drink his mother's milk.
You're doing wrong.
It is a sin.
Aygül!
What? Didn't you say you'd
look after him?
Didn't you say you'd raise him
as long as she lives?
You say Aygül but...
I killed Aygül.
I'll kill an unwanted kid too. Get it?
You'll stick to our agreement.
Don't forget who I am.
Then remember who you are.
Remember what you gave up to live.
I'll keep my promise.
But you'll remember what I told you.
You'll get your revenge from
those who did you harm.
Not from those who are beside you.
Don't make me feel remorse for this child!
You promised!
Aygül. Everything aside.
He's your child.
Even though his father is Alişar...
He's not my child.
Not my child.
I wish I could find your trace
by searching...
...put my face to your trace's dust.
I wish Allah destine it so I can see
your face.
O' Muhammed, I need you.
I wish there was a holy campaign
so I could join.
I wish I could go down in the sands
of the road to the Kaaba.
I wish I could see your face in my dream.
O' Muhammed, I need you.
Ali, Hasan and Hüseyin together...
...their love is in the heart...
...tomorrow in the last judgment...
O' Muhammed, I need you.
He lost that friend somewhere...
...the love is in the heart...
...tomorrow in the last judgment...
O' Muhammed, I need you.
You are loved in every heart...
...by crying in the foreign lands...
I need you, O' Muhammed. I need you.
I need you, O' Muhammed.
Who are you? What are you doing
in these lands?
This is Ertuğrul Bey's lands.
Who are you to question me?
It is time now. Now, you will try what
I taught you, on them.
-Salam Alaikum.
-Alaikum Salam.
Where is my brother Osman?
Don't any of you know?
Don't worry, my nephew.
He must have a reason.
Wherever he is, he will come.
No, uncle. No. He won't come. He is riding
his horse to bring more trouble.
Not at all, brother. Let's wait.
If he went to Kulucahisar,
he will pay dearly. Very dearly.
Turks are coming!
Open the doors! Ertuğrul's son,
Osman is here.
They came to retake the castle,
with three men!
Keep laughing, sons of dogs.
You'll see it soon.
An army of three men.
With 99 names of Allah, who creates when
he wants, who fills our hearts with faith.
My beys, in this meeting, I want to
talk about two issues.
Firstly, there is the matter of security
of Muslims who are in the castle.
Nikola might ask for gold in return
for them. Inshallah, he does that...
...so, we can save our brother by
paying the gold.
Maybe they already killed those
innocent people.
May Allah forbid, brother.
But, this is a probability.
My beys, what do you say? Shouldn't we
send an envoy to save our brothers?
Even if we make an agreement,
it doesn't mean that he will keep it.
My nephew is right, he isn't the man
of his word.
Nikola is a devil. His horns should
be ripped.
What do you say, my beys? If this council
takes the decision of war...
...we should talk about how will we mobilize
our troops and which bey will attack which gate.
My bey, instead of sitting here like this
by putting our faith in the...
...agreement with the infidel, we should
talk about how we will beat the enemy.
If we will save our brothers by paying
gold, I say, we should do it.
When will we take the castle!
When we are ready. Of course, if my absent
brother doesn't do anything unprepared.
Aygül. You will stay here. Take him.
Aygül, take him, my girl. Come on.
It's not the time to be stubborn.
Hold him.
Take him to his grandfather.
He should look after his groom's son.
I'll so he can die of a heart attack, right?
You have no one else left than your father.
Come on, don't be stubborn. He'll learn
when the time comes. Hold him.
Come, my girl. Come on.
Come on. Don't leave the tent.
Bala. They say that Osman went to
the castle. Is it true? I'm talking to you, Bala.
-Nobody knows where Osman goes.
-You seem like you know it?
No. I don't know either. But whenever Osman
disappears like this, he returns with trouble.
What does your mouth speak of again,
Hazal Hatun?
You are getting mad very fast, Bala.
I grew up in a bey's tent. I know what
I speak of.
Then, your ears should be listening now.
Mother Selcan.
Bala.
My pretty girl.
I heard that you travel in the mountains.
Well, I can't say that it doesn't fit you.
Yes, I don't have the time to speak with fancy
words but I should speak two words to stop you.
We didn't grow up in a bey's tent. We got
tanned in the uplands in summer, we froze...
...in the tent in winter. We fought in the war
times and eat afterward.
Now, let's come to the point. In these tents,
as every warrior is under Ertuğrul Bey's protection...
...every woman is under my protection,
remember that.
Where are the beys of the tents?
-The council meeting.
-Good then. I'll see Osman after the meeting.
Ya Hayy!
We met again, Osman.
I'm happy for you, Vladius.
You don't even realize that the time
for a bargain has ended.
A bargain is a sunnah.
You found out that you can't pass
with weapons. Good.
Osman.
So, you are Osman.
-Sheep shepherd Osman.
-So you are the sheep, huh?
When you are a shepherd, you see
everyone as a sheep.
When you are a sheep, you see
everyone as a shepherd.
Isn't the petty tents that you build on
my holy lands, enough?
So it wasn't enough that you tried to
take a castle without considering yourself.
-We took it.
-But you couldn't hold it, Osman.
We like suffering.
What are those? Is it to save your tents?
To take my captives.
Will you take them with the golds
you took from us.
I took this castle with my weapons.
I didn't steal it like you.
Let me see.
Not you. Soldier.
I like the precautions.
No, I wasn't wrong. This is a roman gold.
This is universal.
Even barbarians like you use this gold.
I have nothing to do with golds, Osman.
So there will be no barter.
I will finish you, your alps, and
the rest of the Turks.
Ertuğrul Ghazi's son, Osman!
I neither give up on my weapons nor
on my brothers!
Now, release the captives.
Or else I will cut the throat of this dog.
Don't, Nikola. Don't!
Use your brain, Osman. Do you think you
can leave this castle such as this?
I'll leave as a wolf leaves a heard of sheep.
Now get the captives to the gate or
say farewell to Vladius.
Don't get any closer, infidels.
Step back, dogs!
It's the promise of Ertuğrul Ghazi's son,
Osman! If we live alive, I'll release Vladius.
Do as he says.
No, Nikola. No! No!
Release the captives.
No, Nikola! No! No! No!
Don't leave me alive, Osman. Don't.
Come on.
Soldier!
A master archer should kill Osman,
without hurting Vladius. Get out!
The shop owners were already dying,
my bey. After the conquest of Kulucahisar...
...we gained a second market but we lost
it too now. I don't know what will happen now.
Potter, if you take the floor, speak
with words that will help.
Now is not the time to talk
about money.
-May I enter?
-Come.
It must be important, Baysungur.
We got a word from our scouts.
Osman Bey and his alps...
...are riding towards Kulucahisar.
I knew he would do that. I knew it.
I knew that would happen.
What should I do about this man now?
He acts as you taught him earlier.
Uncle, brother...
Now, isn't it my right to teach
him his place?
Osman...
If Osman went to Kulucahisar castle...
...he must've gone there to see the
situation of the castle he conquered.
While we sit here like this...
...and listen to the problems with money,
if Osman enthused...
...that is for Allah and religion.
Now, who will teach the valiant
who goes to save the Turks...
...from slavery, his place?
You say who?
Ertuğrul Ghazi's son, Savcı Bey will!
He will teach it to his brother,
his own blood!
None should dare to intervene.
Osman Bey! Osman Bey!
You came to save us!
Vladius.
Osman Bey! He is saving us!
Alps!
If you make another move,
I will kill Vladius right here.
Open the gate!
Osman Bey!
-Keep your promise, release Vladius.
-I'll do it when I'm done.
Look at this sheep shepherd.
Open the gates!
Archers!
If they don't release Vladius,
shoot them all.
Come on. Come on, brothers.
Come on.
-Close the gate.
-Keep your promise, Release Vladius.
Shut it.
You bunglers!
You idiots!
You are good for nothing!
Welcome, Selcan Hatun.
Welcome.
-Thank you, Bamsı Bey.
-Your mission was harder than any of ours.
May Allah please you.
It's just getting started.
How is my Ertuğrul Bey?
Tell me about him.
Selcen Hatun, we had better pray.
You also know that we don't give up
on hope from Allah.
Oh, Ertuğrul Bey...
- My Osman went to the castle, right?
- Yes, yes.
Now his brother wants to punish him.
He should pull himself together!
What punishment is this?
Don't worry.
It is not that easy.
Now, I shall go and see what
decision they have made.
- I will come too.
- Eyvallah(thank you) Selcen Hatun.
O The Healer
O The Healer.
Vladius is here!
Open the doors!
Are they gone?
A Roman...
after being in this situation...
will do a certain thing, Nikola.
Are you going to comit suicide?
How do you want to die, Vladius?
By your sword.
Roma's noble son Vladius,
As a result of your mistake...
are you ready to die?
I am.
I am Savcı Bey, who Ertuğrul Ghazi
chose to be Head Alp...
in the tribe meeting, in front of
every Bey.
Osman Bey disobeyed my order...
and endangered the captives' lives.
When he returns to the tribe,
he'll be arrested.
Savcı...
Haste makes wastei my brother.
Maybe Osman saves the captives and return.
Will you arrest your brother then?
Gündüz Bey, this is a issue of justice.
Not a family issue.
Eyvallah, Savcı Bey, Eyvallah (Okay).
But don't forget, Osman saved your life
by disobeying you.
So, will he disobey me every time?
Am I a Head Sheep or a Head Alp?
Savcı Bey...
Savcı Bey.
You shall not make a big decision when
our Ertuğrul Bey is in bed.
Such decisions are not made with rank
but with nobleness!
Being Head Alp doesn't mean you
can do this.
I wish you had talked to Osman Bey
this way, Bamsı Bey.
- Because he acts like a Kayı Bey.
- He actually does...
Because with every move he makes
shows he deserves to be a Kayı Bey.
Welcome, aunt, but as you can see,
I am new also.
Selcan Hatun.
Don't exacerbate.
Now it is time to talk about how
we can get Kulucahisar back.
Are you ready to lose the last hope
of Roma in Turk war...
and leave me all alone?
Are you ready to destroy Roma's
future for your pride?
- This is what Romans do!
- This was what Romans did!
Because even if they had died, they would
know Roma would stand tall!
Romans survived thanks to this honour,
Nikola!
If you are smart, you get stronger,
Vladius, if you are strong, you be proud.
Roma will be stronger, Vladius.
Roma will be stronger, and then we will
deserve to be proud!
- I can't live like that, Nikola.
- You have to!
You have to take it all just like I did
when Geyhatu insulted me!
Vladius...
Kill me.
- Do you want to die?
- Kill me.
Who is going to kill your father's
murderers?
Who!?
Who is going to take revenge for your father?
Are you going to kill yourself while
your father's murderers are there?
Why are you not talking?
Why are you silent?
Talk!
Save your dignity!
Be quiet.
I am talking to my son.
Talk!
What are we going to do with
Yavlak Arslan?
Can Yavlak restrain Ertuğrul's sons?
If Geyhatu wants, I'll schackle them
and make them obey.
Enough!
I have listened so much lately.
Ertuğrul's Beys and sons talked
all the time.
I listened to them.
Do you know why?
Because you can't get to know a
silent man.
They talked...
I listened.
Geyhatu is wise.
Geyhatu doesn't know anything.
He wants to learn.
Bring me news...
from Osman and Bamsı.
If you wish, I want to do more.
Make Osman and Bamsı...
obey.
I don't care about the others.
You need to authorise me for that.
I authorised you...
in all the tribes in the region.
From now on, you are Bey of the Beys.
You won't regret it.
Make them obey.
Don't worry, glorious Geyhatu.
Geyhatu is not glorious, but he
wants to be.
Mongke is not here now!
Mongke is dead!
My Osman Bey is coming!
Osman Bey is coming!
Thank you my Allah.
Be ready, Alps.
My Bey, are we still arresting him?
My order is certain.
Is your meeting done, brother?
Have you talked it through?
You disobeyed again, Osman Bey.
You'll be arrested.
How is going to do that, brother?
Alps!
Arrerst him!
Hay Allah!
Don't you dare!
I am talking to you Alps!
Alps!
Arrest him!
Lower your swords.
Lower your swords!
Bamsı Bey.
Don't mess things up.
You are talking to the Head Alp!
Head Alp Savcı Bey.
Head Alp Savcı Bey!
Hey people!
Look at here!
If you want to see a Head Alp...
Look at him.
If you want to see a Kayı Bey...
Hey Mashallah(praise be)!
He saved your captive brothers...
while you are just talking and doing
nothing!
Now who dares to touch him?
I dare !
- You, ha?
- Yes, I dare!
Enough!
Enough already!
I am your big brother!
Do you hear me?
You neither listen to me, nor
consult to me.
You just fight like cat and dog!
Enough now, I won't see you like this
again. Osman!
No one is going to disobey the Head Alp.
Savcı! No one is going to arrest
their brother because of this.
Brother!
You are bossing me around.
Hands off my brother.
Savcı Bey!
Come!
Our Bey is dying!
Our father is dying!
Father!
Whatever happens, they are brothers
in the end of the day.
They are sons of Ertuğrul Ghazi.
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com